Cover **Letter**

[Tarragona, Catalunya, 2023]

To Whom it May Concern,

I am a Senior Graphic Designer from Chile, with a solid background in graphic communication, illustration, and more recently, web development. Over the past years, my journey has taken me to Canada and New Zealand, where I not only perfected my English but also immersed myself in independent design projects, expanding my skills and international experience.

Key Highlights:

- > Fluency in English: My immersion in English-speaking environments equipped me with the language skills necessary to collaborate effectively with a diverse range of colleagues and clients.
- > Web Development: With my recent transition to web development, I gained experience in coding, UX design, and front-end development, adding an interactive dimension to my design capabilities.
- > Illustration: My proficiency as an illustrator enhances my ability to bring a unique artistic perspective to projects.

My proven track record includes leading design teams, mentoring new designers, and delivering a wide array of successful graphic materials. These experiences have cultivated my time management skills and honed my ability to excel under pressure.

Additionally, I'd like to mention that I arrived to Spain in order to attend a fullstack programming bootcamp, expanding my knowledge and skills in development.

I am excited to discuss how my diverse skill set can benefit your company. You can review my portfolio at https://rodrigorosalesmoya.netlify.app/. To schedule an interview, please contact me at: rodrigo.rosalesmoya@gmail.com.

Sincerely,

Rodrigo Rosales Moya

Rodrigo Rosales Moya

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | ILLUSTRATOR | **DEVELOPER**

- **4** +34 657 82 78 03
- Tarragona, Spain

- rodrigorosalesmoya.netlify.app/
- in linkedin.com/in/rodigorosalesmoya
- © @rod.illustration





Education

September - December 2022 **FULL STACK BOOTCAMP.**

> ISDI Coders (fmr. SkyLab); Barcelona, Spain

March 2007 - December 2011

BACHELOR'S DEGREE. GRAPHIC DESIGN

Duoc UC; Santiago, Chile

Tech Stack























Work **Experience**

July 2012 - Present

(Santiago, Chile)

October 2014 - October 2017

April 2012 - October 2014

January 2011 - December 2011

Freelance Designer - Illustrator

> Mezcla Studio

Senior Graphic Designer

> RAP S.A. - Schopdog

Art Director

> Aji - Promotional Marketing

Graphic Producer

> Pedro, Juan & Diego - Ad. agency

wacom





Languages

English: Fluent

Spanish: Native or Bilingual

About me

I'm Rodrigo, an experienced art director with a background in graphic design, illustration, and web development. Living in Canada and New Zealand improved my English fluency. I recently completed a Fullstack web development bootcamp, merging design and development to create unique designs. I thrive on design and programming challenges, ready to apply my versatile skills to exciting projects, thanks to my diverse background.

Hobbies & Interests











